[ED]
Oh, hey, Deyano-chan, I have a question for you. Is this a good time?
Uh-huh.
Um...
I don't want to study because I don't understand the point of studying.
Well, I don't think you have to do it, but if you can't study, the number of people who make fun of you will increase as you grow up.
And it's hard to live because you don't know anything about the world.
The rest is up to you. I'll leave it to you.
If you don't wanna cry...
No, no, no, no!
Nooo,No,No,No,No,No
No, no, no, no, no, no
No,No,No,No,No,No
No, No, No, No, No, No, No!
Stop praying for love!
You can't stop this love!
How dare you point that gun at me?
I'll kill you all inara
This ano channel is a short version
Ano Chan Carta
Please.
Still going?
Let's still go.
Let's think about it some more.
Yes, yes, yes, let's think about it some more.
I'd like to have a better one that we can use.
I'd like you to make a carta with the people watching.
I want you to buy these things, and if you're a kurugur, I want you to do it
I want you to think about it with me.
The pictures are hard to draw, anyway...
Do you have words in your head?
Yes, a lot of words come to mind.
What is it, by the way?
Well, I'm not sure.
I think this one is easier.
Is this one better?
This one.
This one? Can you draw it?
I'm just showing a little respect.
Okay, I'll take this one, please.
This way.
What is it?
This is Konishi through the camera.
Well, it looks like we are going to play in Japanese, doesn't it?
Konishiki is a Japanese speaker, so I respect him.
Do you like it that way?
I have no idea.
You had some ideas, didn't you?
One of the candidates was Kinko through the camera.
But it was too dangerous, so Tatsuru Konishi took the place of Kinko.
This is what Hana-chan wrote earlier.
It's amazing, she wrote it with a touch like Mimi Hazama's.
I was lost.
She wrote it like a quote.
That girl.
[fast forward]
Okay, I'll open it.
And then, Dangerous?
Dangerous?
What do you mean, "Dangerous"?
Dangerous? What does that really mean?
Dangerous.
Dangerous?
Oh, so I'm making something totally different?
No, I'm making Dangerous Grandpa.
Are you okay? Dangerous Dangerous.
That doesn't mean anything.
Yes, it is.
Uncle Russ.
You know, there are people who suddenly get naked when they walk outside.
Or an uncle who dresses like this on the train.
It's dangerous.
Some people do it when they're close enough to see it.
Have you heard about it and seen it?
Yes, I did.
And I saw a guy with messy hair and glasses.
There was an interpreter there at the time, too, so I told him there was a guy with really messed up hair and glasses.
I said, "There's this guy..." and her husband also had messy hair and glasses.
So I said, "Oh, no, that's not me.
If it's messy, you should be careful with our manager.
In the city, on the street.
Sometimes they ride bicycles on the streets.
Please be very careful.
The world is a very dangerous place.
There are so many dangers!
Subscribe to Amachan Channel!